A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation photographs FA003
Rockefeller Archive Center
- United States - Hawaii - Humanities and Arts
  - University of Hawaii - Philosophy (Box 48, Folder 1150)
- United States - Illinois
  - Southern Illinois University - Symposium of New Orchestral Music (Box 48, Folder 1151)
  - University of Chicago (Box 48, Folder 1152)
    Microphotography, microfilm, buildings.
  - Institute of Psychoanalysis - Chicago (Box 48, Folder 1153)
    Offices, interiors.
  - North Western University - Neurology (Box 48, Folder 1154)
  - University of Chicago - Psychiatry (Box 48, Folder 1155)
  - University of Chicago - Atomic Research Institute (Box 48, Folder 1156)
  - University of Chicago - Chemistry (Box 48, Folder 1157)
  - University of Chicago - Endocrinology (Box 48, Folder 1158)
  - University of Chicago - Light Velocity (Box 48, Folder 1159)
  - University of Chicago - Meteorite Studies (Box 48, Folder 1160)
  - University of Chicago - Molecular Spectra (Box 48, Folder 1161)
  - University of Chicago - Spectroscopic Biology (Box 48, Folder 1162)
  - University of Chicago - Zoology (Box 48, Folder 1163)
  - Malaria (Box 48, Folder 1164)
  - Dappert and Fergusen - Report on Malaria and Mosquito at Flerrin for the Season (Box 48, Folder 1165)
  - Public Health (Box 48, Folder 1166)
  - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Report (Box 48, Folder 1167)
    Archaeology, architecture.
  - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, Microphotography 1938 Davis, W. (Box 48, Folder 1168)
  - University of Chicago - Social Science Research Building (Box 48, Folder 1169)
  - University of Chicago - Race Relations (Box 48, Folder 1170)
    Minorities, schools.
  - University of Chicago - Communications (Box 48, Folder 1171)
- United States - Illinois - Medical Sciences
  - Institute of Psychoanalysis - Chicago (Box 48, Folder 1153)
  - North Western University - Neurology (Box 48, Folder 1154)
  - University of Chicago - Psychiatry (Box 48, Folder 1155)
- United States - Illinois - Natural Sciences and Agriculture
  - University of Chicago - Atomic Research Institute (Box 48, Folder 1156)
  - University of Chicago - Chemistry (Box 48, Folder 1157)
  - University of Chicago - Endocrinology (Box 48, Folder 1158)
  - University of Chicago - Light Velocity (Box 48, Folder 1159)
  - University of Chicago - Meteorite Studies (Box 48, Folder 1160)
  - University of Chicago - Molecular Spectra (Box 48, Folder 1161)
  - University of Chicago - Spectroscopic Biology (Box 48, Folder 1162)
- United States - Illinois - Declinations
  - University of Chicago - Zoology (Box 48, Folder 1163)
- United States - Illinois - Malaria
  - Malaria (Box 48, Folder 1164)
  - Dappert and Fergusen - Report on Malaria and Mosquito at Flerrin for the Season (Box 48, Folder 1165)
- United States - Illinois - Public Health Demonstrations
  - Public Health (Box 48, Folder 1166)
- United States - Illinois - Humanities and Arts
  - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute - Report (Box 48, Folder 1167)
  - University of Chicago - Oriental Institute, Microphotography 1938 Davis, W. (Box 48, Folder 1168)
- United States - Illinois - Social Sciences
  - University of Chicago - Social Science Research Building (Box 48, Folder 1169)
  - University of Chicago - Race Relations (Box 48, Folder 1170)
  - University of Chicago - Communications (Box 48, Folder 1171)
- United States - Indiana
  - Indiana University - Summer Institute for Teachers (Box 48, Folder 1172)
    Teachers, classrooms, schools.
  - University of Notre Dame - Bacteriology (Box 48, Folder 1173)
    Equipment, machinery, laboratories.
- United States - Indiana - Declinations
  - University of Notre Dame - Bacteriology (Box 48, Folder 1173)
- United States - Iowa
  - Medical Science (Box 48, Folder 1174)
    Hospitals, schools, laboratories, demonstrations, group portraits.
  - Natural Sciences (Box 48, Folder 1175)
  - Lenox String Quartert - Grinnell College (Box 48, Folder 1176)
    Performing arts, music, group portraits.
  - University of Iowa - Drama Arts Building (Box 48, Folder 1177)
    Theater, performing arts, set design.
  - University of Iowa - University Theater (Box 48, Folder 1178)
    Performing arts, drama, theater.
- United States - Iowa - Medical Sciences
  - Medical Science (Box 48, Folder 1174)
- United States - Iowa - Natural Sciences and Agriculture
  - Natural Sciences (Box 48, Folder 1175)
- United States - Iowa - Humanities and Arts
  - Lenox String Quartert - Grinnell College (Box 48, Folder 1176)
  - University of Iowa - Drama Arts Building (Box 48, Folder 1177)
  - University of Iowa - University Theater (Box 48, Folder 1178)
- United States - Kansas
  - Public Health
    Schools, Children, Group Portraits, Privies, Sanitation,
  - Menninger Foundation - Psychiatric Aides
    Mental Health, Nurses, Training,
  - University of Kansas
    Laboratories, Hospitals, Buildings,
- United States - Kentucky
  - Hookworm 1
    Diseases, Hookworm, Dispensaries, Demonstrations, Families, Children, Houses, Schools, Group Portraits,
  - Hookworm 3
    Diseases, Hookworm, Dispensaries, Demonstrations, Families, Schools, Children, Houses, Case studies,
  - Public Health 1 1921-1924
    Health, Nursing, Hospitals, Clinics, Dispensaries, Wards, Patients, schools,
  - Public Health 2 1921-1924
    Health, Clinics, Midwives, Nurses, Children, Sanitation, Dispensaries, Inocculations,
  - Lock - The Health Campaign in Clay County Kentucky, 1913
    Diseases, Hookworm, Clinics, Dispensaries, Sanitation, Families, Houses, Case Studies,
  - Lock - Story of Harlan County Dispensary, Kentucky Novemeber 7, 1913
    Diseases, Hookworm, Clinics, Dispensaries, Rivers, Towns, Group Portraits, Children,
  - McCormick - Rowan County Dispensary, Kentucky 1913
    Diseases, Hookworm, Schools, Children, Families,
  - Heiser - Report on a visit to a Hookworm Infested County
    Diseases, Hookworm, Families, Houses, Children, Case Studies, Group Portraits,
  - Hookworm 2
    Disease, Hookworm, Dispensaries, Clinics, Demonstrations,
- United States - Louisiana
  - Leprosy
    Diseases, Leprosy, Hospitals, Quaratine centers,
  - Tulane University
    Animals, Animal testing, experiments, Operations, Kennels, Dogs, mice,
  - Hookworm
    Diseases, Hookworm, Dispensaries, Exhibits, Group Portraits, Families, Children, Schools, Privies,
  - Malaria 1
    Diseases, Malaria, Sanitation, Drainage Ditches, Bayous,
  - Malaria 2 1922-1930
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Houses, Rivers, Bayous,
  - Petritz - Experimental Malaria Control by Scrrening as applied to Typical Tenant
    Diseases, Malaria, Houses,
  - Public Health 1925-1929
    Diseases, Typhoid, Syphillis, Clinics, Children, Group Portraits, Families, Tonsilitis, Sanitation, Slaughter Houses, Privies,
  - Tulane University - Middle American Research Institute 1930-1938
    Art, Sculpture, Architecture, Mayan, Cities, Archaeology, Masks,
- United States - Maryland
  - Chesapeake Biological Laboratory
    Boats, Marine Biology,
  - Johns Hopkins University
    Schools, Buildings,
  - Johns Hopkins University
    Schools, Buildings, Interiors,
  - Johns Hopkins University 1921-1931
    Hospitals, Schools, Group Portraits, Medical Training,
  - Bull - The Distribution of Anopheles Crucians in Maryland
    Diseases, Malaria, Sample collection, Equipment,
  - Malaria 1921
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Woodlands,
- United States - Massachusetts
  - Harvard Law School
    Group Portraits,
  - Harvard University
    Hospitals, Maternitity Wards, Facilities, Equipment, Interiors,
  - Woods Hole
    Oceanography, Marine Biology, Buildings,
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
    Buildings, Aerial Views, Specimines, Laboratories,
  - George Robert White Fund
    Buildings,
  - Harvard University
    Buildings, Schools, Group Portraits,
  - Harvard University - Fogg Museum
    Buildings, Performing Arts, Music, Orchestras,
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology
    Computers,
  - Massachusetts Institute of Technology - Differential Analyer
    Machinery,
- United States - Michigan
  - University of Michigan
  - Hookworm 1
- United States - Minnesota
  - University of Minnesota
    Schools, Aerial views,
  - University of Minnesota - Agricultural Biochemestry, Biophysics
    Schools, Laboratories, Equipment, Experiments,
  - University of Minnesota - Employment and Unemployment Study
    Meetings, Group Portraits,
  - University of Minnesota - Intergovernmental Relations
- United States - Mississippi
  - General
    Forestry, Sanitation, Roads, Towns,
  - Nutrition - School Health Services
    Schools, Students, Wells, Medical Exams, Physical Education, Fencing,
  - Trains - Flood
    Railroads, Trains, Natural Disasters, Floods,
  - Free Southern Theater
    Theater, Drama, Performing Arts,
  - Hookworm 1
    Diseases, Hookworm, Dispensaries, Group Portraits, Physicians, Schools, Children, Case studies, Privies, Sanitation, Houses,
  - Hookworm 2
    Diseases, Hookworm, Dispensaries, Group Portraits, Families, Children, Case studies, Privies, Sanitation, Houses,
  - Hingst - Annual Report of Malaria Control in Canton, Mississippi by Anti Mosquit
    Diseases, Malaria, Houses, rivers, drainage ditches, woodlands,
  - Howard - Final Report of Experimental Campaign for the Control of Malaria by Ant
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Woodlands, Rivers, Houses,
  - Howard - Report of the Hinds County Anti Malarial Campaign for the period June
    Diseases, Malaria, Landcapes, Roads, Rivers, Woodlands, Drainage Ditches,
  - Howard - Special Report on the Use of the Gambusia Affinis as an agent
    Diseases, Malaria, Woodlands, Rivers, Houses, Fisheries, Drainage Ditches, Spraying, Equipment, Vehicles,
  - Malaria 1919 - 1925
    Diseases, Malaria, Displays, Exhibits, Newspapers,
  - Public Health 1
    Health, Clinics, Child welfare, flood relief, Houses, Children, Group Portraits, Diseases, Typhoid, vaccinations, transportation,
  - Public Health 2
    Diseases, Typhus, Vaccinations, Children, Group Portraits, Dispensaries, Clinics, Houses, Sanitation, privies,
  - Shipp - Narrative Report of Public Health Activities in Flooded Areas
    Natural Disasters, Floods, Flood relief, Families, Towns, Rivers, Red Cross,
- United States - Missouri
  - St. Louis Symphony - Young Composers Program
    Music, Performing arts, Orchestras,
  - Stephens College
    Schools,
  - Washington University - Botany, Cell Chemistry, Neurophisiology
    Equipment, Laboratories,
  - Washington University - Nueropsychiatry, Public Health Teaching
    Nurses, Patients, Hospitals, Diseases, Polio, Rehabilitation,
  - Malaria
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches,
  - Boyd - Report to the Missouri State Board of Health on the Influence of Malaria
    Diseases, Malaria, Group Portraits, Children, Rivers, Ditches,
- United States - Montana
  - Public Health 1928-1929
    Native Americans, Group Portraits,
- United States - Nebraska
  - University of Nebraska - College of Medicine
    Aerial views, buildings, schools,
- United States - New Hampshire
  - Dartmouth College - Borison, Herbert
    Portraits,
- United States - New Mexico
  - Santa Fe Opera House
    Opera, Performing Arts, Theaters,
  - Public Health
    Health, Sanitation, Houses,
- United States - New York
  - Cornell University - Animal Nutrition - Babatunde, Gabriel
    Libraries, Research, Portraits,
  - Mary McClellan Hospital
    Hospitals, Buildings, Furniture,
  - New York University - School of the Arts
    Performing Arts, Dance, Schools,
  - Sarah Lawrence College - Aeolian Chamber Players
    Performing Arts,
  - Theater in the Streets
    Performing Arts, Drama,
  - Albany Medical School
  - New York City Department of Hospitals Reseach Council
    Hospitals, Laboratories,
  - Skidmore College - School of Nursing 1939, 1941
    Children, Nurses, Medical exams,
  - Cornell University - Radiation, Long Island Biological Association
    Plants,
  - Cornell Clinic
    Hospitals, Clinics, Interiors, Patients,
  - Public Health
    Nurses, Farming,
  - Paper Bag Players
    Theater, Performing Arts, Drama,
- United States - North Carolina
  - Hookworm 1 1911-1914
    Diseases, Hookworm, Communities, Families, Children, Demonstrations, Sanitation, Privies,
  - Hookworm 2 1911-1914
    Diseases, Hookworm, Demonstrations, Families, Children, Sanitation, Privies,
  - Hookworm 3 1911-1914
    Diseases, Hookworm, Children, Families, Sanitation, Privies,
  - Malaria 1923, 1927
    Diseases, Malaria, Group Portraits, Families, Houses, Rivers, Drainage Ditches,
  - Experimental Education
    Aerial Views, Schools,
  - University of North Carolina - Population Studies Center
  - University of North Carolina - Genetics
    Genetics, Agriculture, Food, Corn,
  - Public Health
    Health, offices, Group Portraits, Vehicles, Cars,
  - Public Health 1918-1920, 1923, 1933, 1939
    Diseases, Typhus, Vaccinations, Group Portraits, Clinics, Privies, Sanitation,
  - Register - The Log of the Health Lizzie an Account of the Work
    Dental care, group Portraits, clinics, health officers,Diseases, Typhus, vaccinations, children,
  - Washburn, B. E. - Report of Cooperative Work in North Carolina Against Soil
    Sanitation, Privies, Schools, Buildings, Houses, Tuberculosis, Typhus, Hookworm, Diseases,
  - Taylor - A Report to the North Carolina State Board of Health on the Investigati
  - School Health Service 1942, 1946-1948
    Schools, Health services, Children, Medical Exams, Classrooms, Physical education, nutrition,
  - University of North Carolina - Drama 1947
    Drama, Performing Arts, Theater,
  - University of North Carolina - Drama
    Performing Arts, Drama, Theater,
- United States - Ohio
  - Public Health
    Group Portraits, Food, Children,
  - University of Cincinatti
    Hospitals, Aerial Views, Mental Health, children,
  - Ohio Wesleyan Perkins Observatory
    Observatories, Astronomy,
- United States - Oklahoma
  - Public Health
    Sanitation, Privies,
- United States - Oregon
  - University of Oregon - Medical School - Library
    Schools, Libraries, Auditoriums,
- United States - Pennsylvania
  - Public Health
    Demonstrations, Aerial Views,
  - Lankenau Hospital, Villanova University Playwright Workshop
    Hospitals, Writers,
  - Pennsylvania University, Persbyterian Hospital
    Hospitals, Animal testing, Laboratories, Facilities,
  - Phipps Institute
    Clinics, Medical Exams, Group Portraits, Segregation, Children, Diseases, Rickets,
- United States - Philippine Republic
  - Leprosy 1923
    Diseases, Leprosy, Group Portraits, Nurses, Doctors, Patients, Hospitals,
  - Scarlet Fever 1917-1927
    Diseases, Scarlet Fever, Hospitals, Boats, Buildings, Nurses, Patients, Wards,
  - Hookworm
    Diseases, Hookworm, Malaria, Paris Green, Pestisides, Rivers, Privies, Sanitation,
  - Malaria 1
    Diseases, Malaria, Mosquitos, Paris Green, Pesticides, Plants, Rivers, Spraying, Equipment,
  - Administration, Cholera, Health
    Group Portraits, Health Officials, Disease, Cholera, Equipment,
  - Heiser Trip Diaries, volume 2, 1916
    Group Portrait,
  - International Health Board - Zamboanga General Hospital Training School
    Group Portraits, Medical Students,
  - University of the Philippines
    Schools, Group Portraits, J.G. Harrar, Classrooms,
  - University of the Philippines 1921, 1971
    Hospitals, Schools, Buildings, Clinics,
  - Nursing 1922-1936
    Nurses, Group Portraits, Families, Children, Health, Sanitation, Vaccination, Medical Exams,
  - University of the Philippines - School of Hygene and Public Health
    Hospitals, Schools, Construction,
  - Industrial Center, Utility Systems Survey
    Construction, Meetings,
  - Philippine Fishery Commission
    Fisheries,
  - University of the Philippines - Utility Systems Survey - Progress Report
    Building Plans,
  - Dy, F. J.
    Portraits, Field Stations,
  - Joaquin, Nick
  - Magsaysay Award Foundation - Library - Opening Scrapbook, 1963
    Libraries, Group Portraits,
  - Philippine Normal College - Drama
  - Silliman University - Asian Library Development Report, September 2, 1958
    Libraries, Schools, Group portraits,
  - Silliman University - Music Research - Folk Arts Ensemble
    Performing Arts, Music, Schools,
  - University of the Philippines - History, Library listening room
    Libraries, Audio Visual materials,
  - University of the Philippines - Economic Development, Public Administration
    Schools, Construction, Libraries, Ceremonies, Graduations, Students,
  - Malaria 2
    Diseases, Malaria, Experiments, Specimines, sample collection, landscapes,
  - Public Health 1
    Schools, Students, Celebrations, Parades, Military, Transportation, carts, animals, food, rice, landscapes, volcanos, houses, indiginous peoples,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Creation of the Institute
    speakers, dedication ceremony,signing, group photos,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Buildings 1
    construction, buildings, landscape, artwork,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Buildings 2
    microfilm reader, library, buildings, landscape,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Laboratories and Technicians
    laboratories, research, agriculture, rice, testing, equipment, plants,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Machinery
    machinery, machines, fields, farming, rice,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Miscellaneous
    landscape, rice fields, ceremony, logo, seal, views, charts, group photos,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Rice Fields
    rice fields, workers, buildings, landscape, views, paddies,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Rice Yield Trials
    fields, agriculture, rice, crops,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Trustees Visits 1960-1967
    trustees, group photos, group portraits, visiting,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Visitors - Individuals
    visitors, group photos,
  - International Rice Research Institute - IRRI - Visitors - Groups
    meetings, group photos, group portraits,
  - University of the Philippines - Agriculture, Home Economics, International House, Southeast Asian Scholarships
    building, people, agriculture, crops, home economics, food preparation, group photos, teaching, education, laboratory work, classroom, meeting,
- United States - Puerto Rico
  - Medical Care - Bayamon Regionalization
    Health care, medical exams, children, families, Buildings, Hospitals,
  - General
    Farming, Agriculture, Laborers, Families, Children, Food, Sugar, tobacco, Houses, Group portraits,
  - University of Puerto Rico - Medical Care, Medical School
    School, Doctors, Nurses, Patients, Medical exams, children, childbirth, laboratories, medical students, group Portraits,
  - University of Puerto Rico - School of Tropical Medicine, University Hospital
    Schools, Hospitals, Buildings, Exteriors, Interiors, Wards, Operating Rooms, Patients, Classrooms, Libraries, Group Portraits, Laboratories,
  - Hospitals
    Hospitals, Buildings, Exteriors,
  - Hookworm 1910, 1920, 1924, 1926, 1927
    Diseases, Hookworm, Group Portraits, Case Studies, Children, Houses, Indiginous Peoples, Privies, Sewers, Sanitation,
  - Earle - Demonstrations in Malaria Control - Puerto Rico Progress Report, 1925-
    Diseases, Malaria, Irrigation, Drainage Ditches, Canals, Swamps,
  - Malaria 1921, 1926-1929, 1936
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Irrigation, Agriculture, Dams,
  - Green - Preliminary Report on Anopheles Mosquito Reduction and its Relation to
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Construction, Field Offices, Fisheries, Sample collection, Spraying, equipment,
  - Earle, Johson and Morales - Report of Malaria Surveys of Puerto Rico, 1924-1925
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Canals, Irrigation, Towns, Cities, Buildings, Houses, Medical Exams, Children,
  - Green - Report of an Investigation in a Section of Puerto Rico to determine
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Landscapes, Towns, Sample collection, Sewers,
  - Green - Second Preliminary Report on Anopheles Mosquito Reduction
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Swamps, Lakes, Irrigation, Farming,
  - Tuberculosis, 1939
    Diseases, Tuberculosis, Children, Quarantines, Housing,
  - Humanities and Arts
    Actors, Drama,
- United States - Rhode Island
  - Brown University - Applied Mathematics
    Students, Classrooms,
- United States - American Samoa
  - General
    Villages, Indigenous Peoples, Houses, Group Portraits,
  - Hookworm
- United States - South Carolina
  - Hookworm
    Diseases, Hookworm, Sanitation, Privies, Case Studies, Demonstrations,
  - Malaria 1923, 1926
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Railroads, woodlands,
  - Public Health 1921, 1930
    Health services, families, Group Portraits, Motion Pictures, Vehicles,
- United States - Tennessee
  - Southern Highland Craftsmen
    Handicrafts, woodworking, sewing, weaving, basketry, Applied Arts, Performing Arts, Dancing, Fairs, Exhibits,
  - Vanderbilt University - Nutrition in Pregnancy
    Nutrition, Patients, Laboratories, medical exams, Prenatal care,
  - Vanderbilt University Medical School
    Schools, aerial views,
  - Vanderbilt University - Nursing
    Hospitals, classrooms, dormitories,
  - Hookworm 1912-1914
    Diseases, Hookworm, Case Studies, Families, Children, Schools, Group Portraits, Dispensaries, Field Laboratories,
  - Malaria 1923, 1926, 1938
    Diseases, Malaria, Pesticides, Oil, Spraying, Paris Green, Equipment,
  - Public Health 1921, 1926
    Health Services, Sanitation, Nutrition, Dental Hygenie, schools, children, Diseases, Typhus, vaccinations,
  - Tuberculosis Clinic in Williamson County
    Nurses, Clinics, Vaccinations, Diseases, Tuberculosis, Children,
- United States - Texas
  - University of Texas - Alcoholism
    Schools, Laboratories,
  - University of Texas - Cytogenetics
    Laboratories, Field Equipment,
  - Malaria 1921-1924
    Diseases, Malaria, Drainage Ditches, Sanitation, Sewers,
  - Magoon, E. H. - Copy of a letter to Dr. M. M. Carrick with photoraphs 1921
    Diseases, Malaria, Sanitation, Inspection, Sewers, Privies, Cisterns, wells,
  - West, A. W. - Wichita County Health Department from a report of the Bureau of
    Sanitation, Privies, Rivers, Drainage Ditches,
  - Public Health 1916-1923
    Sanitation, Privies, Sewers, Exhibits, Drainage Ditches,
  - Hookworm 1924
    Diseases, Hookworm, Case Studies, Families, Children, Dispensaries,
- United States - Utah
  - Utah
    Exhibits, Health services,
  - Utah - Public Health Laboratory
    Laboratories, equipment,
- United States - Virginia
  - Virginia
    Group Portraits, Celebrations,
  - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts - College Drama Festival
    Group Portraits, Audiences, Theater, Performing Arts, Dance,
  - Hookworm 1910-1923
    Diseases, Hookworm, Demonstrations, Group Portraits, Houses, Families, Schools, Case Studies,
  - Malaria (Box 61, Folder 1373)
    Diseases, malaria, demonstrations, exhibits, rivers, drainage ditches.
  - Public Health (Box 61, Folder 1374)
    Sanitation, privies, houses, families.
  - Social Science (Box 61, Folder 1375)
    Newspaper, facsimile.
- United States - Virginia - Malaria
  - Malaria (Box 61, Folder 1373)
- United States - Virginia - Public Health Demonstrations
  - Public Health (Box 61, Folder 1374)
- United States - Virginia - Social Sciences
  - Social Science (Box 61, Folder 1375)
- United States - Washington
  - Seattle Repertory Theater (Box 61, Folder 1376)
  - Seattle Symphony Orchestra (Box 61, Folder 1377)
    Performing arts, music, orchestras, group portraits.
  - University of Washington - Chemistry (Box 61, Folder 1378)
  - University of Washington - Nursing Education (Box 61, Folder 1379)